(Howard:)Hey, put your tie
back in your pants.
(Raj:)Nice place.
(Raj:)Reminds me of my parents'
house back in New Delhi.
- You're kidding.
- No. We are very wealthy.
(Raj:)But the only difference is,
we have more servants.
- More than this?
- More than we can use.
(Raj:)You see, in India,
we don't make the mistake
of letting up poor people
have dreams.
(Seibert:)Ah. There's my band
of brainiacs.
(Seibert:)Where's Dr. Cooper?
(Leonard:)He's tearing the mask off nature
to look at the face of God.
(Seibert:)The board of directors insists
he has a beautiful mind.
(Seibert:)I think he's just bananas.
(Seibert:)Come on, let me introduce you
(Seibert:)to one of the university's
leading donors.
(Raj:)I think we were misled
about the cute girls.
(Seibert:)Mrs. Latham, I'd like
you to meet three
(Seibert:)of our outstanding
young researchers.
(Seibert:)This is Dr. Leonard
Hofstadter,
(Seibert:)Dr. Rajesh Koothrappali
and Howard Wolowitz.
(Mrs Latham:)Well, what happened
to you, Wolowitz,
(Mrs Latham:)couldn't stick with it
long enough to get your PhD?
(Howard:)I'm an engineer.